uscollegesearch.org 2013-05-20

# Colleges and Universities at U.S. College Search

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity. It is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide and to help you in making informed decisions when using our site, products and services. This Privacy Policy will be continually assessed against new technologies,   
business practices and our customers' needs.

Access to and use of the U.S. College Search web site is available only to United States residents who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law. If you do not qualify, you may not use the web site. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, no one under 13 years of age can use the web site. If you are a minor between   
the ages of 13 and 18, you may use the site only in conjunction with your parent, legal guardian or other responsible adult.

As described below, some of your personally identifiable information will be used by us and shared with third parties. By using the web site, you expressly consent to our use of your personal information, and also to the disclosure to and use of this information and also to the disclosure to and use of this information in our efforts contact you and for continued marketing effort by our clients and their agents charged with communicating with our customers and potential customers. You acknowledge that communications to, from and through the U.S. College Search web site are not confidential. You agree that by submitting communications through the U.S. College Search web site, no confidential, fiduciary, contractually implied or other relationship is created between you and U.S.   
College Search other than pursuant to this Privacy Policy. 

**What information do we collect?**

U.S. College Search collects personally identifiable information you voluntarily choose to disclose and "aggregate information" that is automatically collected when you visit the web site.

Personally identifiable information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are and is collected when you choose to request information from our clients. This information can include your name, current e-mail address, programs of interest and other information you choose to provide. If you choose to correspond with us through e-mail, we may retain your e-mail address and messages together with our responses. If you provide us with full address information you may be added to one of our mailing lists from which you may opt   
out at any time by emailing: info@uscollegesearch.org.

Aggregate information is automatically provided by your computer and cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include:

  * referral data (the web sites you visited just before and just after the web site)

  * date and time of your visits

  * pages viewed and time spent at the web site

  * browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform)

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer on the Internet.

**Cookies**

U.S. College Search uses cookie technology to allow us to deliver customized   
information to you and track which site features are most popular. Cookies let sites and advertisers "remember" users across pages of a site and across multiple visits to a site. In addition, your computer may occasionally receive cookies from our advertisers. U.S. College Search does not control these cookies, and they are not subject to our Privacy Policy. You can disable cookies, but doing so may impact the functioning of parts of the U.S. College Search site. 

**How do we use the personal information that you provide to us?**

Broadly speaking, your personal information is used to help match your interests with schools that provide the training you seek. If your search yields no results, we may store your information and send you updates if and when programs you specified do become available. We also use personal information for purposes of administering our business   
activities, providing customer service, and making other products and services available to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the web site, new services and special   
offers we think you will find valuable. 

Sharing Information With Third Parties

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site.  These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address or telephone number) about your visits to this an other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [Opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "opt out")

Information collected in ad delivery

U.S. College Search may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single-pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect. This software provides a limited degree of protection against unauthorized access or disclosure, as well as accidental loss, alteration or destruction.

**Do we comply with legally compelled disclosure of information?**

We may release any private information about you that we possess when we   
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Privacy Policy and/or other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of U.S. College Search, the site users or others.

** Content on US College Search **

The integrity of our web content is important to us. We have taken measures to make sure all web content on our site is original and owned by us or provided with consent by our clients, advertisers, and other contributors. If you believe we have misattributed any content or are infringing on your copyrighted content, please [contact us here.](mailto:info@uscollegesearch.org)

**What about other sites linked to U.S. College Search?**

Many of the links in the U.S. College Search web site allow you to leave the site. Please be aware that once you leave the site and enter another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. U.S. College Search is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by these sites, nor the information or content contained therein. Please read over the rules and policies of these sites before proceeding.

Although our site is called U.S. College Search, we feature a variety of educational options: technical schools, training centers, universities and other institutions that may or may not be classified as colleges.

**U.S. College Search web site accessibility statement**

The majority of the pages on this web site are accessible to individuals with disabilities in accordance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act. In addition, images on our web site are accompanied by alternative text describing graphics if your browser supports the alt-text function. Documents on our web site are generally accessible to users using  
screen-reading software.

**Contact  Us**

If you would like to learn more about our privacy policy, or to access your personally  
identifiable information contained on our website, you may contact us at:

Plattform Advertising

15500 W. 113th St., Suite 200  
Lenexa, KS 66219

By e-mail: info@uscollegesearch.org

By Phone: 913.254.6000

By Fax: 913.538.5078

You will be required to provide identification information to assure that this information is not released to others. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time without prior notification.
